welcome to course six as $0.99
欢迎来到第六课，价格为0.99美元
artificial general intelligence we will
人工智能我们会
explore the nature of intelligence from
探索智能 的 从性质
as much as possible and engineering
尽可能 和 工程
perspective you will hear many voices my
透视你会听到很多声音 我
voice will be that of an engineer our
声音将是 我们的工程师的声音
mission is to engineer intelligence the
任务是工程智能
MIT motto is mind in hand what that
麻省理工学院的座右铭是手头的想法
means is we want to explore the
意思是我们想要探索
fundamental science of what makes an
什么是 基础科学
intelligence system the core concepts
情报系统的核心概念
behind our understanding of what is
我们对 什么是 理解 的背后
intelligence but we always want to
情报， 但我们总是希望
ground it in the creation of intelligent
在创造智能的基础上
systems we always want to be in the now
我们总是希望在现在的系统
in today in understanding how today we
在今天了解今天我们如何
can build artificial intelligence
可以建立人工智能
systems that can make for a better world
可以创造更美好 世界的系统
that is the core for us here at MIT
这是我们在麻省理工学院的核心
first and foremost we're scientists and
首先，我们是科学家和
engineers our goal is to engineer
工程师我们的目标是工程师
intelligence we want to provide with
我们希望提供的情报
this approach a balance to them very
这种方法的平衡 对他们非常
important but over represented view of
重要但过度代表的观点
artificial general intelligence the
人工智能
black box reasoning view where the idea
黑箱推理视图在哪里的想法
is once we know how to create a human
曾经我们知道如何创造一个 人
level intelligence system how will
等级情报系统将如何
society be impacted will robots take
社会受到机器人的影响
over and kill everyone will we achieve a
结束并杀死每个人我们会实现一个
utopia that will remove the need to do
乌托邦将消除这种需要
any of the messy jobs that will make us
任何会使我们陷入困境的工作
all extremely happy those kinds of
所有人都非常开心
beautiful philosophical concepts are
美丽的哲学概念是
interesting to explore but that's not
有趣的是探索， 但事实并非如此
what we're interested in doing I believe
我相信，我们有兴趣 做什么
that from an engineering perspective we
从工程角度来看， 我们
want to focus on the black box of a GI
我想专注于GI的黑匣子
start to build insights and intuitions
开始建立见解和直觉
about how we create systems that
关于我们如何创建 系统
approach human level intelligence
接近人类的智力
I believe we're very far away from
我相信我们距离很远
creating anything resembling human level
创造类似 人类的 东西
intelligence however the dimension of
然而，情报的维度
the metric behind the word Farr may not
Farr这个词背后的指标可能不会
be time in time perhaps through a few
及时通过一些时间
breakthroughs maybe even one
突破甚至可能是一个
breakthrough everything can change but
突破一切都可以 改变但是
as we stand now our current methods as
正如我们现在所说的那样
we will explore from the various ideas
我们将从各种想法中探索
and approaches and the guest speakers
和方法以及 演讲嘉宾
coming here over the next two weeks and
在接下来的 两周 来到这里
beyond our best understanding our best
超越我们最好的理解我们最好
intuition and insights are not yet at
直觉和见解还没有
the level of reaching without a major
达到没有专业的水平
leap and breakthrough a paradigm shift
跨越和突破 范式的转变
towards human level intelligence so it's
对于人类的智力， 所以它是
not constructive to consider the impact
考虑影响没有建设性
of artificial intelligence to consider
人工智能 需要考虑
questions of safety and ethics
安全保护和道德规范 的问题
fundamental extremely important
根本非常重要
questions we it's not constructive to
问题我们不是建设性的
consider those questions without also
考虑也没有这些问题
deeply considering the black box of the
深深考虑的黑匣子
actual methods of artificial
实际的人工方法
intelligence human level artificial
智力人类人工
intelligence and that's what I see what
智力，这就是我所看到的
I hope this course can be its first
我希望这个课程可以成为第一个
iteration its first exploratory attempt
迭代它的第一次探索尝试
to try to look at different approaches
试着看看不同的方法
of how we can engineer intelligence
我们如何设计智能
that's the role of MIT it's tradition of
这就是麻省理工学院的传统
mine in hand it's to consider the big
我手头的是考虑大的
picture the future impact of society 10
图片10社会的未来影响
20 30 40 years out but fundamentally
20 30 40年，但从根本上说
grounded in what kind of methods do we
我们以什么样的方法为基础
have today and what are their
今天有什么，他们是什么
limitations and possibilities of
的局限和可能性
achieving that the black box of a GI
实现 这一 地理标志 的黑盒子
in the future impact on society of
在未来对社会 的 影响
creating artificial intelligence systems
创建人工智能系统
that get become increasingly more
变得越来越多
intelligent the fundamental disagreement
聪明的根本分歧
lies in the fact the the very core of
在于事实的核心
that black box which is how hard is it
那黑盒子 有多难
to build an AGI system how hard is it to
构建一个AGI 系统有多难
create a human level artificial
创造人性化的人造
intelligence system that's the open
开放的情报系统
question for all of us from from Josh
来自约什 的 我们 所有人的问题
Tenenbaum to Andrey Carpathia to folks
Tenenbaum 对 安德烈卡尔帕西亚 的人们
from open AI to Boston Dynamics to the
从开放的AI到波士顿动力学到
brilliant leaders in various fields of
各 领域的 杰出领导者
artificial intelligence that will come
人工智能 会
here that's the open question how hard
在这里，这是一个多么难的问题
is it there's been a lot of incredibly
这是不是很令人难以置信的
impressive results in deep learning in
深刻学习中令人印象深刻的成果
neuroscience and computational cognitive
神经科学和计算认知
science in robotics but how far are we
科学，机器人，但有多远我们
still to go to the AGI that's the
还是去 那是 在 AGI
fundamental question that we need to
我们 需要根本的问题
explore before we consider the questions
在 我们考虑 问题 之前先探讨
the future impact on society and the
未来对社会和社会的影响
goal for this class is to build
这个课程的目标是建立
intuition one talk at a time a project
直觉一次谈一个项目
at a time build intuition about where we
在一个时间建立 关于我们在哪里的 直觉
stand about what the limitations of
站在什么局限
current approaches are how can we close
目前的方法是我们如何关闭
the gap a nice meme that I caught on
差距是我流行的一个很好的模因
Twitter recently of the difference
Twitter 最近 的差异
between the engineering approach at the
在工程方法之间
very simplest of a Google intern typing
最简单的Google实习生打字
a for loop that just does a grid search
一个只 进行网格搜索的for 循环
on parameters for a neural network and
关于神经网络的参数和
on the right is the way media would
在右边是媒体的方式
report this for loop the Google AI
报告此循环Google AI
created its own baby AI I think it's
创造了自己的宝贝 AI 我认为是
easy for us to go one way or the other
我们很容易走这样 或那样的 方式
but we'd like to do both our first goal
但是 我们想要 做到我们的第一个 目标
is to avoid the pitfalls of black box
是为了避免黑匣子的陷阱
thinking of the few
思考少数人
tourism thinking that results in hype
旅游思维导致炒作
that's detached from scientific
那与科学脱节了
engineering understanding of what the
工程了解什么的
actual systems are doing that's what the
实际系统正在 这样做
media often reports that's what some of
媒体经常报道这是什么
our speakers will explore in a rigorous
我们的演讲者将严格探索
way it's still an important topic to
某种程度上， 这仍然是一个重要的课题
explore Ray Kurzweil's on Wednesday
周三探索Ray Kurzweil
we'll look we'll explore this topic next
我们接下来会看到我们将探讨这个话题
week talking about AI safety and
一周 谈论AI安全和
autonomous weapon systems we'll explore
我们将探索自主武器系统
this topic the future impact 10 20 years
这个话题未来 影响10年20年
out how do we design systems today that
我们今天如何设计系统
would lead to safe systems tomorrow
将导致明天的安全系统
still very important but the reality is
仍然非常重要，但现实是
a lot of us need to put a lot more
我们很多人需要 投入更多
emphasis on the left on the four loops
强调四个循环上的 左侧
on creating these systems at the same
在 同一创建这些系统
time the second goal of what we're
时间是我们的第二个目标
trying to do here is not emphasize the
试图在 这里 做 的 并不是强调
silliness the simplicity the naive basic
愚蠢简单天真的基本
nature of this for loop in the same way
这个for循环的性质以 同样的方式
as was the process in creating nuclear
因为是在 创造核过程
weapons before during World War two
第二次世界大战前的武器
the idea that as an engineer as a
作为工程师的想法
scientist that I'm just the scientist is
科学家认为 我只是 科学家
also a flawed way of thinking we have to
还想到一个有缺陷的方式，我们必须
consider the big picture impact the
考虑大局影响
near-term negative consequences that are
近期的负面后果
preventable the low-hanging fruit that
可以预防的低悬果实
can be prevented through that very
可以 通过这种 方式预防
engineering process we have to do both
工程过程我们必须做到这两点
and in this engineering approach we
在这种工程方法中我们
always have to be cautious that just
总是要谨慎 ， 只是
because we don't understand
因为我们不明白
we're just because we our intuition our
我们只是因为我们的直觉而已
best understanding of the capabilities
最好地了解 这些能力
of modern systems that learn that act in
学习这种行为的现代系统
this world seem limited seem far from
这个世界似乎有限，似乎很远
human level intelligence our ability to
人类的智力水平我们的能力
learn and represent common sense
学习和代表 常识
reasoning seems limited the exponential
推理似乎限制了指数
potentially Exponential's could be
潜在的指数可能是
argued and he will growth of technology
争辩说他将增长技术
of these ideas means that just around
这些想法 意味着就在身边
the corner is a singularity
角落是一个奇点
is a breakthrough idea that will change
是一个将 改变的突破性想法
everything we have to be cautious of
我们必须谨慎 的一切
that moreover we have to be cautious of
而且是我们必须要谨慎
the fact that every decade over the past
这是过去每十年的事实
century our adoption of new technologies
世纪我们采用新技术
has gotten faster and faster the the
越来越快了
rate at which a new technology from its
来自它的新技术的速度
birth to its wide mass adoption has
出生到其广泛的大规模应用有
shortened and shortened and shortened
缩短，缩短和缩短
that means that new idea the moment it
这意味着新的想法
drops into the world can have widespread
落入世界可以 广泛传播
effects overnight so as and I think the
一夜之间的效果，以及我认为
in the engineering approach is
在工程方法是
fundamentally cynical on artificial
从根本上说是人为的愤世嫉俗
general intelligence because every
一般情报因为每一个
aspect of its is so difficult we have to
它 的一个方面是如此的困难 ， 我们 必须
always remember that overnight
永远 记住 ， 隔夜
everything can change through this
一切都可以改变
question of beginning to approach from a
开始接近 的问题
deep learning perspective deep
深学习的观点深
reinforcement learning from brain
强化从大脑学习
simulation computational cognitive
模拟计算认知
science from computational neuroscience
来自计算神经科学的科学
from cognitive architectures from
来自认知架构
robotics from legal perspectives and
从法律角度 和 角度来看机器人技术
autonomous weapon systems as we begin to
我们开始使用自主武器系统
approach these questions we need to
处理这些问题 ， 我们需要
start to build intuition how far away
开始建立直觉有多远
are we from creating intelligent systems
我们是从创建智能 系统吗？
the singularity here is that spark that
这里的奇点就是火花
moment when we're truly surprised by the
我们真正感到惊讶的那一刻
intelligence of the systems we create
我们创建的系统的智能
I'd like to visualize it by the by a
我想通过a来想象它
certain analogy that we're in this dark
我们在这黑暗中的某种类比
room looking for a light switch with no
房间寻找 没有 的电灯开关
knowledge of where the light switch is
了解灯开关的 位置
there's going to be people that say well
会有人说得好
it's a smaller the rooms are all smaller
这是一个小的房间都 小
right there and say anywhere we'll be
就在那里，说出 我们会在 哪里
able to find it in any time the reality
能够在 任何 时候 找到它 的 现实
is we know very little so we have to
我们知道的 很少，所以我们必须这样做
stumble around feel our way around to
绊倒了感觉我们的方式
build the intuition a far far away we
建立一个远在我们身边的直觉
really are
真的是
many will speakers here will talk about
许多人会 在这里发言 将谈
how we define intelligence how we can
我们如何定义智能如何
begin to see intelligence what are the
开始看到情报 是什么
fundamental impacts of creating
创造的根本影响
intelligence systems I'd like to sort of
我想要的 情报系统
see the positive reason for this little
看到这个小小的积极原因
class and for these efforts that have
上课和这些努力
fascinated people throughout the century
整个世纪都让人着迷
of trying to create intelligent systems
尝试创建智能系统
is that there's something about human
是有关于 人类 的东西
beings that one that craves to explore
那些渴望探索的人
to uncover the mysteries of the universe
揭开宇宙的奥秘
fundamental in itself a desire to
本身就是一个愿望 ， 根本
not for a purpose and there's often an
不是 出于某种目的而 经常出现这种情况
underlying purpose of money of greed of
贪婪金钱的根本目的
the power craving for power and so on
对电力的渴求等等
but there's seems to be an underlying
但 似乎有潜在的
desire to explore nice little book an
探索欲望可爱的小书的
exploration a very short introduction by
探索一个非常简短的介绍
Stewart Weaver he says for all the
他为所有人说过斯图尔特韦弗
different forms it takes in different
它采取不同的形式
historical periods for all the worthy
所有有价值的历史时期
and unworthy motives that lie behind it
它 背后隐藏着不值得的动机
exploration travel for the sake of
探索旅行的缘故
discovery and adventure is a human
发现和冒险是人类
compulsion a human obsession even it is
甚至是强迫人类的痴迷
defining element of a distinctly human
定义明显人类的元素
identity and it will never rest at any
身份，它永远不会 在任何 地方休息
frontier whether terrestrial or
边境无论是陆地还是陆地
extraterrestrial from 325 BCE with a
从公元前325 与外星
long 7500 mile journey on the ocean to
漫长7500英里的海洋之旅
explore the Arctic to Christopher
探索北极到克里斯托弗
Columbus and his flawed harshly
哥伦布和他的瑕疵严厉
criticized the modern scholarship trip
批评现代奖学金之旅
that ultimately paved the way didn't
最终铺平了道路没有
discover pave the way to colonization of
发现铺平了殖民化的道路
the Americas to the DAR
美洲的 DAR
trip the voyage of the Beagle whilst
跳闸贝格尔 而远航
this planet has gone cycling on
这个星球已经骑自行车了
according to the fixed law of gravity
根据固定的万有引力定律
from so simple a beginning endless forms
从如此简单的开始无尽的形式
most beautiful and most wonderful have
最美丽，最精彩的有
been and are being evolved to the first
已经并且正在发展到第一个
venture into space by Yuri Gagarin first
首先 由尤里加加林冒险进入太空
human in space in 1961 what he said over
1961年人类在太空中所说的话
the radio is the earth is blue it is
收音机是地球是蓝色的
amazing this these are the words they
令人惊讶的是这些是他们的话
think drive our exploration in the
想 推动我们的探索中
sciences in engineering and today an AI
工程科学和今天 的人工智能
and the first walk on the moon and now
第一次登上月球， 现在
the desire to colonize Mars and beyond
殖民火星及 其他地方的愿望
that's where I see this desire to create
这就是我看到的这个愿望 创造
intelligent systems talking about the
智能系统说起
positive or negative impact of AI on
人工智能的积极或 消极 影响
society talking about the business case
社会谈论 商业案例
of the jobs lost jobs gain jobs created
该工作失去 工作取得创造就业机会
diseases cured the autonomous vehicles
疾病治愈了自动驾驶汽车
the ethical questions the safety of
伦理问题的安全性
autonomous weapons of the misuse of AI
滥用人工智能的自主武器
in the financial markets underneath it
在它下面的金融市场
all and they're people many people are
一切， 他们是人很多人 都
spoken about this what drives myself and
谈到这个驱动我自己的事情
many in the community is the desire to
社区中的许多人都渴望
explore to uncover the mystery of the
探索揭开神秘面纱
universe and I hope that you join me in
宇宙，我希望你加入我
that very effort with the speakers that
那个扬声器非常努力
come here in the next two weeks and
来到 这里 ，在未来两周
beyond the website for the course is a
超出该课程的网站是一个
GI that MIT died edu I am a part of an
麻省理工学院死于教育的地理标志我是一个部分
amazing team many of whom you know AGI
令人惊叹的团队，其中许多人都知道 AGI
at MIT that edu is the email where on
在麻省理工学院， edu是电子邮件的地方
slack deep - MIT does slack for
懈怠- 麻省理工学院确实懈怠
registered MIT students
麻省理工学院注册学生
you create account on the website and
你在网站上创建帐户 和
submit five new links and vote on ten to
提交五个新链接并对 十个 投票
vote AI which is an aggregator of
投票AI 是一个聚合器
information a material we've put
信息我们提供的材料
together for the topic of AGI and submit
一起为AGI主题提交
a entry to one of the competitions one
参加 其中一场比赛的参赛者之一
of the three competitions projects that
三个比赛项目中的那个
we have in this course and the projects
我们有这个课程和项目
are dream vision I'll go over them in a
有梦想的愿景我去了他们 在
little bit dream vision angel ethical
有点梦想的天使道德
car and the aggregator of material vote
汽车和物质投票的聚合器
AI we have guest speakers incredible
我们有 非常 好的 演讲嘉宾
guest speakers I will go over them today
演讲嘉宾今天 我将介绍他们
and as before with a deep learning for
和以前一样深入学习
self-driving cars course we have shirts
自动驾驶汽车当然我们有衬衫
and they're free for in-person for
并且他们可以免费 获得
people that attend in person for the
亲自参加的人
last lecture most likely or you can
最后一次 讲座或者你可以
order them online
在线订购
okay dream vision we take the Google G
好的梦想我们采取谷歌 G
dream idea we explore the idea of
梦想我们探索的想法
creativity where it is I ins view of
我认为的创造力
intelligence the mark of intelligence is
情报是情报的标志
creativity this this idea is something
这个想法是创造性的
we explore by using neural networks and
我们通过使用神经网络和
interesting ways to visualize what the
有趣的方式可视化什么
networks see and in so doing create
网络看到并在这样做创造
beautiful visualizations in time through
美丽的可视化 及时通过
video so taking the ideas of deep dream
视频因此采取了深刻的梦想
and combining them together with
并将它们结合在一起
multiple video streams to mix dream and
多个视频流混合梦想和
reality and the competition is through
现实和竞争是通过
Mechanical Turk we set up a competition
Mechanical Turk 我们组建了 一个比赛
of who produces the most beautiful
是谁生产的 最美丽的
visualization will provide code to
可视化将提供代码
generate this visualization and ideas of
生成这种可视化和想法
how you can make it more and more
你怎么能 越来越多
beautiful and how to submit it to the
美丽，如何提交给
competition angel the artificial neural
竞争天使人工神经
generator of emotion and language is a
情感和语言的发生器是一个
different twist on the Turing test where
图灵测试中的不同扭曲在哪里
we don't use words we all
我们不使用的话 ，我们 都
using motions to speak expression of
用动作来表达
those emotions and we create we use an
那些情绪和我们创造我们使用 的
age a face customizable we're 26 muscles
年龄可定制的脸我们是26个肌肉
all of which can be controlled with an
所有这些都可以用 来控制
LS TM we use a neural network to train
LS TM我们使用神经 网络进行 训练
the generation of emotion and the
情感的产生和
competition in you submitting the code
你提交代码的竞争
to the competition is you get 10 seconds
参加比赛你得到10秒
to impress with the these expressions of
用这些表达来打动
emotion the viewer
观众的情感
it's a be testing your goal is to
这是一个可以测试你的目标是
impress the viewer enough to where they
给观众留下足够的印象
choose your agent versus another agent
选择您的代理商与另一个代理商
and those that are most loved the agents
以及那些最受代理人喜爱的人
most loved will be the ones that are
最喜欢的将是是那些
declared winners in a twist we will add
我们将添加 一个扭曲的胜利者
human beings into this mix so we've
人类融入这种混合所以我们已经
created a system that map's our human
创建了一个映射我们人类的系统
faces myself and the TAS to where we
面对自己和TAS到 我们所在的地方
ourselves enter an outcome in the
我们自己进入了结果
competition and try to convince you to
竞争， 并试图说服你
keep us as your friend
让我们成为你的朋友
that's the Turing test ethical car
这是图灵测试道德汽车
building and the ideas of the trolley
建筑和 小车 的想法
problem and the moral machine done here
问题 和道德机器在这里完成
in the Media Lab the incredible
在媒体实验室 里不可思议
interesting work we take a machine
有趣的工作，我们拿 一台机器
learning approach to it and take what
学习它的方法并采取什么
we've developed the deep reinforcement
我们开发了深层加固
learning competition for success 0 9 for
学习竞争成功 0 9 for
the deep traffic and we add pedestrians
交通深度，我们增加了行人
into it stochastic astok irrational
进入随机的非理性
unpredictable pedestrians and we add
不可预知的行人，我们补充说
human life to the loss function where
人生对失去的功能在哪里
there's a trade-off between getting from
来自之间需要权衡利弊
point A to point B so in deep traffic
A点到B点，所以 在深度交通中
the deep reinforcement learning
深层强化学习
competition the goal was to go as fast
竞争的目标是尽快
as possible here it's up to you to
尽可能在这取决于你
decide what what your agents goal is
决定你的代理人目标是什么
there's a parade of front
前面有一个游行队伍
trade-off between getting from point A
从A点起之间的权衡
to point B as fast as possible and
尽可能快地指向B.
hurting pedestrians this is not a
伤害行人这不是一个
ethical question it's an engineering
道德问题这是一个工程
question and it's a serious one because
问题，这是一个严肃的问题， 因为
fundamentally in creating autonomous
从根本上创造自治
vehicles that function in this world we
在这个世界上运作的车辆我们
want them to get from point A to point B
希望他们从 A点到B点
as quickly as possible
尽快
the United States government insurance
美国政府 保险
companies put a price tag on human life
公司 为人的生命设定了价格标签
we put that power in your hands
我们把这种力量掌握在你手中
in designing these agents to ask the
在设计这些代理商时要问
question of a how can we create machine
我们如何创造机器的问题
learning systems where the objective
学习系统所在的目标
function the loss function has human
功能 丧失功能有人类
life as part of it and vote AI is an
生活作为其中的一部分，投票AI是一个
aggregator of different links different
不同链接的聚合器不同
articles papers videos on the topic of
上的主题的文章篇视频
artificial general intelligence where
人工一般情报在哪里
people vote on vote quality articles up
人们对投票质量文章投票
and down and choose on the sentiment of
并且选择了对情绪的看法
positive and negative we'd like to
我们想要积极和消极
explore the different ways to the
探索不同的方式 给
different arguments for and against
支持和反对的不同论据
artificial general intelligence there is
有人工一般情报
an incredible list of speakers the best
一个令人难以置信的发言人名单最好
in their disciplines from Josh Tenenbaum
来自Josh Tenenbaum的学科
PN MIT to Ray Kurzweil at Google to lisa
PN MIT 向谷歌的Ray Kurzweil致lisa
Feldman Barrett and Nader Pinsky from
Feldman Barrett和 Nader Pinsky来自
Northeastern University
东北大学
Andre karpati Stephen Wolfram Richard
Andre karpati Stephen Wolfram Richard
Moyes mark Robert
莫耶斯标志着 罗伯特
Ilya sutskever and myself Josh Tenenbaum
Ilya sutskever 和我自己Josh Tenenbaum
tomorrow I'd like to go through each of
明天我想通过每一个
these speakers and talk about the
这些音箱谈
perspectives they bring
他们带来的观点
that to try to see the approach the
那试试，看看这种方法的
ideas they bring to the table they're
他们带来的想法是他们的
not in most cases interested in the
在大多数情况下并不感兴趣
discussion of the future impact on
对未来的影响的讨论
society without grounding it into the
社会没有把它纳入
expertise into the actual engineering
专业知识进入实际工程
into creating these intelligent systems
创建这些智能系统
so josh is a computational cognitive
所以乔什 是一个计算认知
science expert professor faculty here at
科学专家教授在这里
MIT he will talk about how we can create
麻省理工学院他将谈论我们如何 创造
common-sense understanding systems that
常识性理解 系统
see a world of physical objects and
看到一个物理世界的世界
their interactions and our own
他们的互动和我们自己
possibilities to act interact with
与...互动的可能性
others the intuitive physics how do we
其他直观的 物理怎么办我们
build into systems the intuitive physics
构建直观 物理系统
of the world more than just the deep
世界 不仅仅是 多 深 的
learning memorization engines that take
学习记忆引擎
patterns and learn through supervised
模式和通过监督学习
way to map those patterns to
将这些模式映射到的方法
classification actually begin to
分类实际上开始了
understand the intuitive the
了解直观的
common-sense physics of the world and
世界的常识性的物理 和
learn rapid model based learning learn
学习基于快速模型的学习学习
from nothing learn from very little just
从没有什么可以学到很少的东西
like we do as children just like we do
就像我们像孩子一样做
as human being successfully often only
人类是成功往往只
need one example to learn a concept how
需要一个例子来学习如何 概念
do we create systems that learn from
我们是否创建了可以学习的系统
very few sometimes a single example and
很少有时一个例子和
integrate ideas from various disciplines
整合来自不同学科的想法
of course from neural networks but also
当然，从神经网络也
probabilistic generative models and
概率生成模型和
symbol processing architectures it's
它是符号处理架构
going to be incredible of course from a
将是从不可思议的，当然
from a different area of the world
来自世界不同区域
another incredible thinker intellectual
另一位不可思议的思想家
speaker is Ray Kurzweil he'll be here on
演讲者是Ray Kurzweil他会在这里
Wednesday and 1:00 p.m. and he will do a
星期三 和 下午1点 ，他会做一个
whirlwind discussion of where we stand
旋风讨论我们的立场
with intelligence creating intelligent
智慧创造智能
systems how we see natural intelligence
系统我们如何看待 自然智能
our own human intelligence how we define
我们自己的人类智慧我们如何定义
it how we understand it and how that
我们如何理解它以及如何理解它
transfers to the increasing exponential
转移到指数增加
growth of development of artificial
人工增长的发展
general intelligence
一般情报
something I'm myself very excited about
我 自己非常兴奋的事情
is Lisa Feldman Barrett coming here on
是Lisa Feldman Barrett来这儿
Thursday she's written a book I believe
周四她写了一本我相信的书
how emotions are made she argues that
她认为，情绪是如何产生的
emotions are created that there is a
创造了一种情感
distinction there's a detachment between
区别是 两者之间 存在 分歧
what we feel in our bodies the physical
我们在身体里感受到了什么
state of our bodies and the expression
我们的身体状况和表达
of emotion from from body to the
从身体到身体的情感
contextually grounded to the face
从根本上讲，面对面
expressing that emotion which means now
表达那种现在意味着的情感
why is there as a person who is
为什么会有一个人
psychology person in a fundamental
心理学家的根本
engineering computer science topic like
工程计算机科学专题
AGI because if emotions are created in
AGI 因为如果创造了情感
the way she argues and she'll
她争辩的方式，她会
systematically break it down
系统地分解
that means we're learning societal as
这意味着我们正在学习社会
human beings were learning societal
人类在学习社会
norms of how to express emotion the idea
如何表达情感的规范
of emotional intelligence is learned
学习情商
which means we can have machines learn
这意味着我们可以让 机器学习
this idea it's a machine learn like it's
这个想法是一台机器学得像它一样
a human learning problem it's a machine
一个人类学习问题，它是一台机器
learning problem in a little bit of a
在一点点学习问题
twist she asked that instead of giving
扭曲她问，而不是给予
it talk I have a conversation with her
它说话 我和她谈话
so it's going to be a little bit
所以它会有一点点
challenging and fun and she's great
充满挑战和乐趣，她很棒
looking forward to it and we'll explore
期待 它 ，我们将探讨
different ways that we can get emotion
我们可以通过不同的方式获得情感
expressed through video through audio
通过视频通过音频表达
through the project the angel project
通过项目天使项目
that I mentioned so there's been worked
我提到过，所以一直有效
in reenacting intelligence so well
在如此好地重演情报
reenacting mapping face to face mapping
重新映射面对面映射
different emotions on video that was
视频这是不同的情感
previously recorded so if you can
以前记录过，如果可以的话
imagine that means we can take emotions
想象 这意味着我们可以采取情绪
that we've created the kind of emotion
我们创造了那种情感
creation we've been discussing and remap
创作我们一直在讨论和重新制作
it on previous video that's one way to
这 在以前的视频这是一个办法
see intelligence is taking raw human
看到情报正在接受原始人类
data that we already have and mapping
我们已有的数据和映射
new computer-generated
新的计算机生成
the the underlying fundamentals of human
人类 的 基本面
but the surface appearance the
但表面外观
representation of emotion visual or
表达情感视觉或
auditory is generated by a computer it
听觉是由计算机生成的
could be in the embodied form
可以是体现的形式
[Music]
[音乐]
very important to note for those
非常重要的是要注意那些
captivated by Sofia in the press or have
索菲亚在报刊上着迷或有
seen these videos
看过这些视频
Sofia is an art exhibit she's not a
索菲亚是一个她不是的艺术展览
strong natural language processing
强大的自然语言处理
system this is not an AGI system but
系统，这不是一个 AGI系统，但
it's a beautiful visualization of
这是一个美丽的可视化
embodying of Hollow
空心 的体现
it's a beautiful visualization of how
这是一个如何美丽的可视化
easy it is to trick us human beings that
很容易骗我们人类
there's intelligence underlying
有智慧的基础
something that the emotional expression
情感表达的东西
the physical embodiment and the
物理实施例 和
emotional expression that has a that has
有情感的情感表达
some degree of humor that has some
某种程度的幽默 有一些
degree of wit and intelligence is enough
机智和 智慧 程度 就足够了
to captivate us so that's an argument
吸引我们，这是一个争论
for not creating intelligence from
因为没有创造智力
scratch but having machines at the very
从头开始，但具有 非常 机
surface the display of that emotion the
表现出那种情感的表现
generation the mapping of the visual and
生成视觉和视觉的映射
auditory elements worth underneath it is
在它下面的听觉元素是
really trivial technology that's
非常琐碎的技术
fundamentally relying on humans like in
从根本上依赖于人类像
the sophia's case and in the simplest
sophia的案例和最简单的案例
form we remove all elements of Hajus a
形式我们删除了Hajus的所有元素a
attractive appearance from from an agent
来自代理商的诱人外观
we really keep it to the simplest
我们真的把它保持在最简单的状态
muscles
肌肉
characteristics of the face and see with
面部特征和看见
26 muscles controlled by a neural
26个肌肉由神经控制
network through time so recurrent neural
通过时间网络如此反复神经
network I was TM how can we explore the
网络我是TM 我们怎么能探索
generation of emotion can we get this
我们可以得到这种情感
thing and this is an open question for
事情，这 是一个悬而未决的问题
us too we just created the system we
我们也只是创建了我们的系统
don't know if we can can we get it to
不知道我们是否可以得到它
make us feel something make us feel
让我们感受到让我们感受到的东西
something by watching it express its
通过观察表达它的东西
feelings can it become human before our
感情可以 在我们之前 成为人类
eyes can I learn to by competing against
我 可以通过 竞争 来学习眼睛
other agents a be testing on Turk a
其他代理对土耳其人 一个 被测试
Mechanical Turk can the winners be very
机械土耳其人可以获胜者
convincing to make us feel entertained
说服 让我们感到 愉快
pity love maybe some of you will fall in
可惜的爱情也许你们中的一些人会陷入困境
love with angel here Nate dibinsky on
与 天使爱这里内特dibinsky上
Friday will talk about cognitive
星期五将谈论 认知
modeling architectures so you will speak
建模架构，所以你会说
about the cognitive modeling aspect can
关于认知建模方面 可以
we have a ma can we model cognition in
我们有一个可以模拟认知的马
some kind of systematic way to try to
尝试某种系统的方式
build intuition of how complicated
建立多么复杂的 直觉
cognition is Andre karpati famous for
认知是安德烈卡帕蒂着名的
being the state-of-the-art human on the
作为最先进的 人类
imagenet challenge the representative
imagenet挑战代表
the 95% accuracy performance among other
95％的 准确性表现 等
things he's also famous for his now a
他现在也很有名的东西
Tesla he will talk about the role the
特斯拉，他将谈论 的作用
limitations the possibilities of deep
限制深度的可能性
learning we'll talk as I have spoken
学习我们会像我说的那样说话
about in the past few weeks and
关于 过去几周 和
throughout about our misunderstanding or
关于我们的误解或
our flawed intuition about what are the
我们对于什么是有缺陷的直觉
difficult and what are the easy problems
困难，有什么容易的问题
in deep learning and the power of
在深度学习和的力量
representational learning the ability of
代表性学习的能力
neural networks to form deeper and
神经网络形成更深层次
deeper representations of the underlying
更深层次的基础表征
raw data that ultimately forms
最终形成的原始数据
takes complex information that's hard to
获取难以获得的复杂信息
make sense of and convert it into useful
理解并将其转化为有用的
actionable knowledge that is from a
来自a的可操作知识
certain lens in a certain a certain lens
在某个镜片中 某些镜片
in a certain problem space can be
在一定的问题空间可以
clearly defined as understanding of the
明确定义为理解
complex information understanding is
复杂的信息理解是
ultimately taking complex information
最终采取复杂的信息
and reducing it to its simple essential
并将其简化为简单的必需品
elements representational learning is in
元素代表性学习是在
the trivial case here in drawing having
这里 有 一个简单的 例子
to draw a straight line to separate the
画一条直线 来分隔
blue and the red curves that's
蓝色和红色曲线
impossible to do in the in initial input
在初始输入中无法做到
space on the Left what the act of
左边的 空间是 什么行为
learning is for deep neural networks in
学习是针对深层神经网络的
this formulation is to construct a
这个表述是构建一个
topology under which there exists a
存在的拓扑结构
straight line to accurately classify
直线准确分类
blue versus red that's the problem and
蓝色与红色这是问题 和
for a simple blue and red line
一条简单的蓝色和红色线条
it seems trivial here but this works in
这似乎微不足道，但这适用于
the general case for arbitrary input
任意输入的一般情况
spaces for arbitrary nonlinear highly
高度任意非线性空间
dimensional input spaces and the ability
维度输入空间和能力
to automatically learn features to learn
自动学习要学习的功能
hierarchical representations of the raw
原始的层次表示
sensory data means that you could do a
感官数据意味着你可以做一个
lot more with data which means you can
更多数据意味着你可以
expand further and further and further
进一步扩大和越走越
to create intelligent systems that
创建智能系统
operate successfully with real-world
与 现实世界成功运作
data that's what representational
这些数据 具有 代表性
learning means that deep learning allows
学习意味着深度学习允许
because the arbitrary number of features
因为任意数量的功能
that can be automatically determined you
这可以自动确定你
can learn a lot of things about a pretty
可以学到很多 关于 漂亮 的 东西
complex world
复杂的世界
unfortunately there needs to be a lot of
不幸的是，需要有很多
supervised data there still needs to be
教师数据存在仍需要
a lot of human input Andre and others
很多人类 投入 安德烈和 其他人
Josh will talk about the difference
Josh将谈论差异
between our human brain our biological
我们的人类大脑之间的生物学
neural network and the artificial neural
神经网络与人工神经网络
network the full human brain with 100
100人网络全人类大脑
billion neurons 1000 trillion synapses
十亿个神经元1000万亿个突触
and the biggest neural networks out
和最大的神经网络
there the artificial neural network
那里有人工神经网络
having much smaller 60 million synapses
拥有更小的6000 万个 突触
for ResNet 152 the biggest difference
对于ResNet 152来说，最大的区别
the parameter is a human brain being
该 参数是一个人的大脑是
several orders of magnitude more
几个数量级 以上
synapses the topology being much more
突触显示更多
complex chaotic the asynchronous nature
复杂混乱的异步 性质
of the human brain and the learning
人脑和 学习
algorithm of artificial neural networks
人工神经网络算法
is trivial and constrained with
是微不足道的，受到约束
backpropagation is essentially an
反向传播本质上是一种
optimization function over over a
优化功能超过
clearly defined loss function from the
明确定义的损失函数
output to the to the input using back
使用back输出到输入
propagation to teach to adjust the
传播教导调整
weights on that network the learning
在网络上权衡学习
algorithm for our human brain is mostly
我们人脑的算法大多是
unknown but it's certainly much more
不为人知，但肯定会更多
complicated than back propagation the
复杂而不是反向传播
power consumption the human brain is a
人的大脑是一种耗电量
lot more efficient than artificial
比人工 更有效率
neural networks and there's a very kind
神经网络 ， 非常善良
of artificial trivial supervised
人工琐事监督
learning process for training artificial
学习人工训练的过程
neural networks you have to have a
神经网络， 你必须 有一个
training stage and you have to have an
训练阶段，你必须有一个
evaluation stage and once the network is
评估阶段，一旦网络
trained there's no clear way to continue
训练有没有明确的方法继续
training it or there's a there's a lot
训练它或那里 有很多
of ways but they're inefficient it's not
方式，但他们效率低下，但事实并非如此
designed to do online learning naturally
旨在 自然地 进行 在线学习
to always be learning is designed to be
永远是学习的目的
to learn and then be applied obviously
学习，然后明显应用
our human brains are always learning but
我们的人脑总是在学习但是
the beautiful fascinating thing is that
美丽迷人的是
they're both distributed computation
他们都是分布式计算
systems on a large scale so it's not a
大规模的系统， 所以它不是一个
there's it doesn't ultimately boil down
它最终没有归结为它
to a single compute unit the computation
到单个计算单元的计算
is distributed the back propagation
分布式反向传播
learning process is distributed can be
学习过程是分布式的
paralyzed in a GPU massively paralyzed
在一个大规模瘫痪的GPU中陷入瘫痪
the underlying computational unit of a
a的基础计算单位
neuron is trivial but can be stacked
神经元是微不足道的，但可以叠加
together to form forward neural networks
一起形成前向神经网络
recurrent neural networks to represent
递归神经网络来表示
both spatial information with images and
空间信息与图像和
temporal information we
时间信息我们
the audio speech text sequences of
音频语音文本序列
images and video and so on mapping from
图像和 视频等 的映射从
one-to-one one-to-many many-to-one so
一到一个一个一对多多到这样一个
the mapping any kind of structure vector
映射任何一种结构向量
and time data as an input to any kind of
和时间数据作为任何类型的输入
classification regression sequences
分类回归序列
captioning video audio as output
将视频音频作为输出
learning in the general sense but in a
在一般意义上学习，但在一个
domain that's precisely defined for the
精确定义的域名
supervised training process we can think
我们可以思考的监督培训过程
of the in deep learning case you can
在深度学习案例中你可以
think of the supervised methods where
想想监督方法在哪里
humans have to annotate the data as
人类必须 将数据 注释 为
memorization of the data we can think of
记住我们能想到 的数据
the exciting new and growing field of
令人兴奋的新兴领域
semi-supervised learning where most of
半监督学习的 大部分时间
the data through or through generative
数据通过或通过生成
adversarial networks or through
对抗性网络或通过
significant data augmentation clever
重要的数据增加聪明
data augmentation most of it is done
数据增加大部分已经完成
automatically the annotation process or
自动注释过程或
through simulation and then
通过模拟然后
reinforcement learning where most of the
强化学习的大部分地方
most of the labels are extremely sparse
大多数标签非常稀疏
and come rarely and so the system has to
并且来得很少，因此系统必须这样 做
figure out how to operate in the world
弄清楚如何 在全球运营
with very little human input very little
人力投入很少很少
human data we can think of that as
人类数据我们可以将 其 视为
reasoning because you take very little
推理因为你很少
information from our teachers the humans
来自我们老师的信息
and transfer it across generalize it
并将它转移 到一般化它
across to reason about the world and
对世界和世界的理性
finally unsupervised learning the
终于无人监督学习了
excitement of the community that promise
许诺 社区兴奋
the hope you could think of that as
你 能 想到的， 作为希望
understanding because ultimately it's
理解，因为最终它是
taking data with very little or no human
用很少或没有人的数据来获取数据
input and forming representations that
输入和成型表示，用于
that data is how we think of
这些数据是我们的想法
understanding requiring making sense of
理解需要理解
the world without strict input of how to
世界没有严格的投入如何
make sense of the world the kind of
理解世界的那种
process of discovering information maybe
发现信息的过程也许
discovering new ideas new ways to
探索新思路新途径
simplify the world to represent the
简化世界来代表
world that you can do new things with it
你可以用它做新事物的世界
the new is the key element there
新的是 那里的关键因素
understanding
理解
and Andre and Ilya and others will talk
安德烈和 伊利亚等人会谈
about the certainly the past but the
关于肯定过去但是过去
future of deep learning where is it
深度学习的未来在哪里
going to go
要去
is it overhyped underhyped what is the
是不是夸大了 什么是 低于 什么的
future will the compute of cpu GPU si
未来将是cpu GPU si 的计算
Asics continue with the breakthroughs
Asics 继续取得突破
the Moore's law in its various forms of
摩尔定律的 各种形式的 法律
massive parallelization continue and the
大规模并行化继续和
large datasets with tens of millions of
拥有数千万的大型数据集
images grow to billions and trillions
图像增长到数十亿和数万亿
will the algorithms improve is there a
算法会有改进吗？
groundbreaking idea that's still coming
开创性的想法仍在继续
look with Jeff hiddens capsule networks
看看 Jeff Hiddens胶囊网络
is there fundamental architectural
有基本的建筑
changes to neural networks that we can
我们可以改变神经网络
come up with that will change everything
拿出 这 将改变一切
that will ease the learning process
这将简化学习过程
they'll make the learning process more
他们会使学习过程更多
efficient or we'll be able to represent
高效或 我们能够 代表
higher and higher orders of information
越来越高的信息秩序
such that you can transform knowledge
这样你就可以改变知识
between domains and the software
域和软件之间
architectures that support intensive
支持密集的架构
florida pi torch i would say last year
佛罗里达州火炬 我去年会说
and this year will be the year of deep
今年将 是 深刻 的一年
learning frameworks so those will
学习框架，所以那些意志
certainly keep coming in their various
肯定会继续他们的各种各样
forms and the financial backing is
形式 和财政支持 是
growing and growing the open challenges
不断增长和发展开放的挑战
for deep learning really a lot of this
深度学习真的很多
course is kind of connected to deep
当然是一种连接 到深
learning because that's where a lot of
学习，因为那是很多的地方
the recent breakthroughs that inspire us
最近的突破激励着我们
to think about intelligence systems come
思考 情报系统来了
from but the challenges of many the need
从但许多 需求 的挑战
the ability to transfer between
两者之间转移的能力
different domains as in reinforcement
不同的领域， 如在强化
learning and robotics the need for huge
学习 和机器人学 需要巨大的
data in an official learning that we
我们 官方 学习的数据
still need supervised data an ability to
仍然需要监督数据的能力
learn in an unsupervised way is a huge
以无人监督的方式学习是一件巨大的事
problem and not fully automated learning
问题 而不是完全自动化的学习
there's still a degree a significant
还有一定程度的重要性
degree of hyper parameter necessary with
必要程度的超参数
the reward functions the loss functions
奖励起着损失的作用
are ultimately defined by humans and
最终由人类和
therefore are deeply flawed when we
因此，当我们处于严重缺陷时
release those systems into the real
将这些系统发布到真实系统中
world
世界
there is no ground truth for the testing
测试没有根据
set and the goal isn't achieving a class
设定，目标不是实现一个阶级
high classification on a trivial image
在平凡的 图像 上的高分类
classification localization detection
分类定位检测
problem but rather to have a autonomous
问题，而是要有一个自主的
vehicle that doesn't kill pedestrians or
不会杀死行人的车辆
an industrial robot that operates in
在中国运营的工业机器人
jointly with other human beings and all
与 其他人和所有人共同合作
the edge cases that come up how does
边缘情况 如何出现
deep learning methods how do machine
深度学习方法怎么做机器
learning methods generalize over the
学习方法概括于此
edge cases the weird stuff that happens
边缘情况 发生 了奇怪的 事情
in the real world those are all the
在现实世界中， 这些都是
problems there Stephen Wolfram will be
斯蒂芬沃尔夫勒姆会有问题
here on Monday evening at 7 p.m. has
这里在星期一晚上晚上7点 有
done a lot of amazing things I would say
我会说很多很棒的事情
is very interesting from his recent
他最近 很 有意思
interest in knowledge based programming
对基于知识的编程的兴趣
Wolfram Alpha I think is the fuel for
Wolfram Alpha的，我认为是燃料
most middle school and high school
大多数初中和高中
students now for the first time taking
学生们现在第一次服用
calculus I pray probably go to Wolfram
微积分我祈祷可能去Wolfram
Alpha to answer their own questions but
阿尔法回答他们自己的问题但是
more seriously there is a a deep
更严重的是有一个深刻的
connected graph of knowledge is being
连接的知识图正在形成
built there with the Wolfram or Wolfram
用Wolfram 或Wolfram在那里建造
Alpha and Wolfram language that steel
Alpha和Wolfram语言表示 钢铁
will explore in terms of language an
将探讨语言方面的问题
interesting thing he was part of the
他有趣的事情是他的一部分
team on arrival that worked on the
队伍抵达 ， 关于工作
language if for those of you are
语言， 如果你是那些人
familiar the arrival were a alien
熟悉的到来是一个外星人
species spoke with us us humans through
物种通过我们与人类交谈
a very interesting beautiful complicated
一个非常有趣的美丽复杂
language and he was brought in as a
语言和他被带入了
representative human to interpret that
有代表性的人来解释那个
language just like in the movie he was
语言就像在电影中，他
represent that in real life and you used
表示 在现实生活中，你使用
the skills that him and his son
他和他儿子的技能
Christopher used to analyze this
克里斯托弗曾经分析过这个
language very interesting that process
语言非常有趣，那个过程
is extremely interesting I hope he talks
非常有趣，我希望他说话
about it and his background with
关于它和他的背景
Mathematica and new kind of science the
Mathematica 和新的科学
sort of another set of ideas that have
排序另一套是有想法的
inspired people in terms of creating
在创造方面激发了人们的灵感
intelligence systems is the idea that
情报系统就是这样的想法
from very simple things were very simple
从非常简单的事情 很简单
rules extremely complex patterns can
规则极其复杂的模式可以
emerge his work was cellular automata
他的工作是细胞自动机
did just that taking extremely simple
这样做非常简单
mathematical constructs here with
数学结构在这里
cellular automata these are these are
细胞自动机这些都是
grids of computational units that switch
切换计算单元的网格
on and off in some kind of a predefined
某种预定义的打开和关闭
way and only operate locally based on
方式， 只在 本地 运作
their local neighborhood and somehow
他们的当地社区 ，不知何故
based on different kinds of rules
基于不同的规则
different patterns emerge here's a three
不同的模式出现在这里是三个
dimensional cellular automata with a
具有一维的细胞自动机
simple rule starting with nothing with a
简单的规则从一开始就 没有
single cell they grow in really
真正 成长的单细胞
interesting complex ways this emergent
有趣的复杂方式 出现了
complexity is inspiring it's the same
复杂性激发了它的灵感
kind of thing that inspires us about
有点激励我们的事情
neural networks that you can take a
你可以采取的神经网络
simple computational unit and when
简单的计算单位和何时
combined together in arbitrary ways can
以任意 方式组合在一起可以
form complex representations that's also
形成复杂的表示这也是
very interesting you can see knowledge
非常有趣，你可以看到知识
from a knowledge perspective you can see
从知识的角度 你可以看到
knowledge formation in the same kind of
知识形成在同一类型中
way simplicity at a mass distributed
分散的质量方式简单
scale resulting in complexity next
规模导致复杂性
Tuesday
星期二
Richard Moyes from article 36 coming all
来自第36条的理查德莫耶斯全部来了
the way from UK for us we'll talk about
我们将谈谈 从英国到我们的路
it works with autonomous weapons systems
它适用于自主武器系统
works with also nuclear weapons but
与核武器一起工作但是
primarily autonomous weapon systems and
主要是自主武器系统和
concern legal policy and technological
关注法律政策和技术
aspects of banning these weapons there's
那些禁止这些武器的方面
been a lot of agreement about the safety
关于安全问题已经达成了很多共识
hazards of autonomous systems that make
自制系统的危害
decisions to kill a human being
决定杀一个 人
mark Robert CEO of Boston Dynamics
波士顿动力的 标志 罗伯特CEO
previously a long time ago faculty here
以前很久以前的教师在这里
at MIT will talk about will bring robots
麻省理工学院将谈论将带来机器人
and talk to us about his work of robots
和我们谈谈他的机器人工作
in the real world as doing a lot of
在现实世界中做了很多
exciting stuff with humanoid robotics
令人兴奋的 人形机器人
and any kind of robots operating on legs
以及任何一种在腿上操作的机器人
it's incredible
这太不可思议了
work extremely exciting and gets to
工作非常令人兴奋，并得到
explore the idea of how difficult it is
探索它有多困难的想法
to build these robot systems that
构建这些机器人系统
operate in the real world from both the
从 现实世界中运作
control aspect and from the way the
控制方面和从方式
final result is perceived by our society
最终结果被我们的社会所感知
it's very interesting to see when
这是 非常有趣的，看看当
intelligence in robotics is embodied and
机器人技术的智能体现和
then taking in by us and what that
然后接受我们和那是什么
inspires fear excitement hope concern
激发恐惧兴奋希望关注
and all the above Ilya sutskever is
以上所有Ilya sutskever都是
expert in many aspects of machine
机器的许多方面的专家
learning
学习
he is the co-founder of open AI I'll
他是我打开AI的联合创始人
talk about their different aspects of
谈谈他们的不同方面
game playing that they've recently been
他们最近去过的比赛
exploring about using deeper enforcement
探索使用更深层次的执法
learning to play our K games in D on the
学习在 D上玩我们的 K游戏
deep mind side using deep reinforcement
深刻的思想 方面使用深层加固
learning to beat the best in the world
学会打败世界上最好的
that the game of go in 2017 the big
那场比赛在2017年 大了
fascinating breakthrough achieved by
通过实现引人入胜的突破
that team with alphago zero training an
那个拥有alphago 训练的 队伍
agent that through self play playing
代理人通过自我玩耍
itself not on expert games so truly from
本身并不是真正的专家游戏
scratch learning to beat the best in the
划伤学习打败了最好的
world including the previous iteration
世界包括前一次迭代
of alphago
alphago
we will explore what aspects of the
我们将探讨哪些方面
stack of intelligent robotic systems
堆栈的智能机器人系统
intelligent agents can be learned in
智能代理可以学习
this way so deep learning the
这种方式如此深入学习
memorization the supervised learning
记忆监督学习
memorization approach it looks at the
记忆方法它看起来
sensor data feature extraction
传感器数据特征提取
representation learning aspect of this
代表性的学习方面
taking the sensor data from camera light
从摄像机灯处获取传感器数据
our audio extracting the features
我们的音频提取功能
forming higher-order representations and
形成高阶表示和
on those representations learning to
在那些学习的表示
actually accomplish some kind of
实际上完成某种
classification regression task figuring
分类回归任务计算
out based on the representation what is
根据表示是什么
going on in the raw sensory data and
继续在原始的感官数据和
then combining that data together to
然后将这些数据结合在一起 ，以
reason about it and finally in the
关于它的理由并最终在
robotic domains taking it all together
机器人领域将它们整合在一起
as with human
和人类一样
industrial robotics autonomous vehicles
工业机器人自动驾驶汽车
taking all together and actually acting
全力以赴 ，实际行动
in this world with the effectors and the
在这个世界上有效 应器 和
open question is how much of this AI
悬而未决的问题是多少这个 AI 的
stack can be learned that's something
堆栈可以学到 东西
for us to discuss to think about that a
让我们来 讨论去思考 一个
Leo will touch on with deeper
狮子会更深入地触及
enforcement learning we can certainly
执法学习我们当然可以
learn representations and perform
学习表达和表演
classifications state-of-the-art better
分类最先进的 更好
than human and image classification
比人类和图像分类
imagenet and segmentation tasks and the
imagenet 和分段任务和
excitement of deep learning is what's
深刻学习的兴奋是什么
highlighted there in the red box can be
在红色框中突出可以 有
done end to ends
完成端到端
raw sensory data out to the knowledge to
将原始感官数据输出到知识中
the output to the classification can we
我们可以输出分类
begin to reason is the open question
开始理性是一个悬而未决的问题
with the knowledge based programming
以知识为基础的 编程
that Stephen Wolfram will talk about can
Stephen Wolfram会谈到的 可以
we begin to take these automatically
我们开始 自动采取这些
generated high order representations and
生成高阶表示和
combine them together to form knowledge
将它们结合在一起形成知识
bases to form aggregate graphs of ideas
基础形成思想的汇总图
that can then be used to reason and can
然后可以 用来推理并且可以
we then combine them together to act in
然后我们将它们组合在一起 起作用
the world for whether in simulation with
世界 是否在模拟中
arcade games or simulation of autonomous
街机游戏或自主模拟
vehicles or biotic systems or actually
车辆 或生物系统或实际上
in the physical world with robots moving
在机器人移动 的物理 世界中
about can that end end from raw sensory
关于那可能最终从原始的感官结束
data to action be learned that's the
要了解的数据是行动的
open question for for artificial general
人为的一般问题
intelligence for this class can this
这类的智慧可以这样
entire process be end to end can we
我们可以将整个过程端到端
build systems and how do we do it that
构建系统，我们如何做到这一点
achieve this process end to end in the
在端到端实现这个过程
same way that humans do we're born in
我们生来就像人类一样
this raw sensory environment taking in
这种原始的感官环境中服用
very little information and learn to
很少的 信息和学习
operate successfully in arbitrary
以任意方式成功运作
constraints arbitrary goals and to do so
限制 任意目标并这样做
we have lectures we have three projects
我们有讲座， 我们有三个项目
and we have guest speakers from various
我们邀请 各位 嘉宾 发言
disciplines I hope that all these voices
学科我希望所有这些 声音
will be heard and will feed a
将被听到并将提供一个
conversation
会话
artificial intelligence and it's
人工智能 和它的
positive and it's concerning effects in
积极的，它涉及到的 影响
society and how do we move forward from
社会， 我们如何 从 前进
an engineering approach the topics will
主题将采用工程方法
be deep learning deep reinforcement
深入学习深层次的强化
learning cognitive modeling
学习认知建模
computational cognitive science emotion
计算认知科学情感
creation knowledge based programming AI
创建基于知识的编程AI
safety with autonomous weapon systems
自主武器系统的安全性
and personal robotics with human
和人类的个人机器人
centered artificial intelligence that's
中心人工智能这
for the first two weeks of this class
在本课程的前两周
that's the the part where if you're
如果 你是 这样的那部分
actually registered students that's
实际注册的学生是
where you need to submit the project
你需要 提交项目
that's when we all meet here every every
那是我们每个人 在这里见面 的时候
night with the incredible speakers but
晚上与令人难以置信的扬声器，但
this will continue we already have
这将继续我们已经拥有
several speakers scheduled in the next
几个发言者预定在下一个
couple of months yet to be announced but
几个月 还没有公布 但是
they're incredible and we have
他们是不可思议的 ，我们有
conversations on video and we have new
视频对话，我们有新的
projects
项目
I hope this continues throughout 2018 on
我希望这会持续到整个2018年
the topics of IAI ethics and bias
IAI道德和偏见的主题
there's a lot of incredible work in we
我们有很多令人难以置信的工作
now have a speaker there coming on the
现在有一个扬声器在那里
topic of how do we create artificial
我们如何创造人工的主题
intelligence systems that I do not
智力系统，我没有
discriminate do not form the kind of
歧视不形成那种
biases that us humans do in this world
我们人类 在这个 世界上 所做的偏见
that are operating under social norms
在社会规范下运作
but our reasoning beyond the flawed
但我们的理由超越了缺陷
aspects of those social norms with bias
具有偏见的社会规范的各个方面
creativity as with a project of dream
创造力与 梦想 的 项目
vision and beyond there is so much
愿景和远远超出了那么多
exciting work in charin using machine
使用机器 在 charin 工作令人兴奋
learning methods to create beautiful art
学习方法，创造 美丽的艺术
and music brain simulation neuroscience
和音乐 大脑模拟神经科学
competition in neuroscience shockingly
神经科学的竞争令人震惊
in the first two weeks we don't have a
在前两周我们没有
competition neuroscience speaker which
竞争神经科学演讲者
is a fascinating perspective brain
是一个 迷人的视角 大脑
simulation or neuroscience in general
模拟或神经科学一般
computational neuroscience is a
计算神经科学是一种
fascinating approach from the from the
来自的迷人方法
muck of actual brain work to get the
实际的脑力劳动渣土获得
perspective of how our brain works and
透视我们的大脑是如何运作的
how we can create something that mimics
我们如何能够创造的东西 ， 模仿
that resembles the fundamentals of what
这类似于 什么 的基本原理
makes our brain intelligent and finally
让我们的大脑变得聪明起来
the touring test the traditional
传统的巡回测试
definition of intelligence defined by
定义的智能定义
Alan Turing was grounded in natural
艾伦· 图灵以自然为基础
language processing creating chat BOTS
语言处理创建 聊天BOTS
that impress us that amaze us and trick
给我们留下深刻印象的是令我们惊讶 和诡计
us into thinking they're human we will
我们认为 他们是我们的人类
have a project and a speaker on natural
有自然的项目和演讲者
language processing in March with that
三月语言处理
I'd like to thank you for coming today
我要 感谢你今天来
and look forward to seeing your
期待 看到你的
submissions for the three projects thank
三个项目的提交感谢
you very much
你非常 喜欢
[Applause]
[掌声]